filmyfriday.com 2014-04-02

# Privacy | Latest in Bollywood, Movie Review, tv news & Celebrity hot photos

FilmyFriday.com has created this privacy statement in order to demonstrate our website commitment to privacy. The following discloses the information gathering and dissemination practices for this Web site: FilmyFriday.com  
Information Automatically Logged  
We use your IP address to gather broad demographic information which allows us to understand better the demand, and what users would like to see more of on our website. All of the information logged is only used for web-statistics purposes such as number of pageviews, hits, etc. 

Advertisers  
We use an outside ad company to display ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies. Cookies received with banner ads are collected by our ad company, and we do not have access to this information.  
* Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site.  
* Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet.  
* Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

Public Section  
This site makes collection of flash movies, sound loops and tutorials. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information. 

External Links  
This site contains links to other sites. FilmyFriday.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. 

Data Quality/Access  
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying information previously provided:  
Mailing List: http://www.FilmyFriday.com

Security  
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. 

Disclaimer  
Filmyfriday.com delivers content from third-parties editor, Filmyfriday.com does not have any control over these contents. The links and contents provided through Filmyfriday.com are the property of the third-parties owners. In no case Filmyfriday.com might be taken responsible for any abuse, opinion, information, link, image or any digital material provided through Filmyfriday.com. Filmyfriday.com does not represent or endorse the accuracy, correctness or reliability of any advice, opinion, statement or other information displayed, uploaded or distributed through any web site hyperlinks. You acknowledge that any reliance upon any such opinion, advice, statement or information shall be taken at your own sole risk.

Contacting the Web Site  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us using feedback form.

**Tags:** [Google](http://www.filmyfriday.com/tag/google), [privacy statement](http://www.filmyfriday.com/tag/privacy-statement)
